We are joining. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah.
For the glory. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah.
So, 逆行動 最悪のそう
来るべき 感激 物さ 燃えを
Hey, if you wanna win, you gotta play smart
You're not enough to chance, the wise will take it all
Very happy, hell is that you're a toy
So I can't be good, that's good
Handlawnしてく人生の thoughts
I'm going to die, don't move
You're right, when all is good
You're right, if you wanna play
Fly and feelして,時はもう満ちた
We're shot in, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Full of glory, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,結晶とした光を,今とした世界をする
We're shot in, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Full of glory, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,核心と栄光を戻そう
Hasushin to運命をはじめよう
Hey, wait for me, won't ya?
What's wrong with you?
A smokescreen, you're a squirrely human, aren't you?
We need to get out of here
Hurry and make that portal thingy back to the divine what's it
Yeah, here we go
We're almost there
You can't escape
Casting Hell's Fire
Not bad
Not bad at all
I suppose I'll just have to make sure we meet up again real soon
That was way too close
Seiya?
What'd you do that for?
I need to train, like now
Get out!
What?
More exercise?
Well, I don't have a choice
You saw how strong she was
Way tougher than that slime
She is one of the four heavenly kings
I'm gonna stay in this room
I'll leave when I'm ready
When the time comes, I'll buzz you
Till then, stay away
What do you mean by ready?
I've had it with all this waiting around
Time to use this thing, Aria, let me
I beseech you
Oh, magical crystal ball
Seer of three thousand realms
If danger runs free, show it to me
Hey, are you two stalking me?
I feel like I'm being stalked
A note for the goddess and hero
The two of you better show up soon
Because if you don't, this little town is history
Please, don't do this
I'm begging you
I'm slicing off everyone's heads
Let's say one resident every ten minutes
Oh my
The red fountains that humans make are just so pretty
So let's paint the town red
I thought I told you not to come in here until I called for you
Well, this is urgent
It's bad
Chaos Machina is on a rampage
The bloodshed won't stop unless we do something to help
We have to hurry back
Nah, bro
I haven't finished blasting my quads
There are people dying and you're blasting out quads, bro
Calm down
Didn't you tell me that time passes way more slowly in the divine realm?
That may be true, but it's not like it stands completely still
So what kind of ratios are we working with here?
I'm not the goddess of maths
Ten minutes on Gaya Brande
That's like 16 hours for us
What's the problem?
We totes got plenty of time left
Even if you're right
A hero should move a little faster when there are lives at stake
Now let's see who's up on the chopping block
I think this lucky man will be next
Oh no
Papa!
No!
Don't hurt him!
How cruel
It's too much
Open!
Doorway to the other world
I said I didn't want to leave until I'm good to go
Are you kidding me?
Nina's father is about to be killed
What?
Hey!
Did you hear me?
I did
Not yet
Listen
I get how scary this is
But your stats give you at least some chance of winning
And I'll have your back with my recovery magic
So don't worry
Who said I was?
Please!
If you die, then you just get sent back to where you came from
But if they die, that's it!
There's no coming back for any of them!
No!
Stop!
I'm begging you!
Don't hurt my papa, please!
Oh, don't worry, little girl
You won't feel lonely because you won't be alone
After I'm done dealing with your daddy
I'll make sure you join him right away!
Don't you care Nina's in danger?
This girl gave you her lucky flower charm
How can you just keep doing nothing?
Yeah, now that you mention it
I think my hunch was right about this item being cursed
Maybe why we ran into that beast in the first place
I blew it
I totally messed up
I never should have summoned you to begin with
Cause you're really just afraid, aren't you?
Is that why you've been acting so cautious?
Well, is it?
Huh?
You coward!
Who cares how powerful you are?
You're the worst hero I've ever laid eyes on
If I die, the town dies
And it won't be long till the whole world follows
Get it now?
I can't afford death
That's why I've been training so hard
Wait, what are you suiting up for?
Isn't it obvious?
No, no way!
He did all that in such a short amount of time
It's enough to defeat Chaos Machina
I'm perfectly prepared
I'm 100% ready for this
Great, that's more like it
I'll make a path to the town square
So we can rescue them straight away
Doorway to the other
How he would you do that for?
Idiot
Make it somewhere farther away
Otherwise she'll finish off that guy and dumb kid
As soon as she sees us
You got a point
But would you mind holding off
On bopping a goddess on the head?
Oh, sure
I should be more careful
I wouldn't want to pick up any cootie germs
My hair is clean, you six-year-old meathead!
Stop it! Please! Don't do anything bad to Pop!
Ah!
Ten minutes is a long time to wait, huh?
Know what? I've changed my mind
Let's make it five minutes
Unfortunately, that means time's up, Pop!
No!
Blame it on your no-show hero!
Wind Blame!
Huh? When'd he get that move?
Yes, I had a feeling you'd come back eventually
Way to leave a girl hanging
I guess this hero's not just short on chivalry
Oh, that's a little rich, don't you think?
You're a bully who takes advantage of the helpless
So say the sneaky creeps
Who tried to ambush me while I was distracted
Who said that you were the one I was trying to hit?
Ah! Thank goodness!
I'm glad you're okay!
Thank you for saving my life!
I owe you one, sir!
So that's how it is
I've seen how I see
You guys played me and I totally fell for it
What is this?
It's like he's a different person
His ability level outranks mine
I see!
So you can scan targets, too
What you think?
Nice stats, am I right?
If you want to throw in the towel, now's your chance
All right, then
Seems like I'm gonna have to take this a bit more seriously
Release!
Oh, you thought you'd won already?
Well, I've got some bad news
Real fighters who play on expert mode
Always have a little something extra hiding up their sleeves
Um, Seiya?
Watch out!
All of her numbers skyrocketed
Come on!
Just when I thought we'd finally caught up!
Okay, time to show me what you're made of, big boy!
Ready or not, here I come, hero!
She's fast!
Swinging that sword like a bad metaphor!
So you can still keep up with my moves, eh?
I wonder if you're one of those guys
The type with a sharp intuition
Yeah, that's right!
Having greater stats doesn't guarantee a big win
You can't underestimate battle instinct and strategy
How troubling!
A troublesome hero indeed!
I'm sure I'll beat you, but I would prefer to be double sure
Get ready!
Here comes my special technique!
I call it demonic curse!
Did you hear that?
Be careful!
Here's a secret
A real, real fighter who plays on expert mode
Always has a little something extra
Hiding under the little something extra!
She doesn't sound like she's messing around
What could she be up to?
Hey, what the room are you doing?
Oh, you'll see
It's the demonic curse, of course
With this overwhelming power
I shall deliver death to the hero!
I'm so confused
Uh, hold on!
Micro-bikini demon isn't her true form?
You gotta be kidding me!
It's stronger than a D-class demon lord!
Even the Saiya's combat smarts!
This looks bad!
Do you now understand the difference in our power?
Surely even you agree that you've no chance of victory!
Just one blow!
One blow and all of it will take to separate your head from your body!
I had no idea
Geafriya Day would be such a terrible world!
I'm sorry!
Please forgive!
What? Impossible! How could this be?
Hold on a second. Say, his stats are too low to survive that.
Did I misread something? No.
Then it must be... the Fake Out skill!
Time for me to give him a quick scan.
A lock? He's definitely using Fake Out.
That sneaky little meathead!
Again? How rude!
What, you?
It's not like I'm curving on you.
Now I'm really gonna keep looking.
Mega McPower!
Come on!
Oh, goodness, my eyes are about to pop out!
Gonna dig deeper, starting!
You can do it! Put your mind into it!
You did it, girl! You finally got the goodies!
What is all this?
These figures are almost five, now ten times higher!
He's got more skills, too!
Wait, there wasn't enough time for that to happen.
So then, he must have started using Fake Out after his first round of training.
He was already stronger than Chaos Machina from the get-go.
He was just grinding this whole time!
This guy is unhinged!
I mean, he's a complete and utter nut job!
Guess you're tougher than I expected!
Whatever!
I'll summon all my magic into my fist using this ability!
The demonic and reach!
Turning you and this whole pathetic little town into...
Where'd you go?
When did you learn the flight skill?
How is that even possible?
She's one of the four heavenly kings.
Very powerful.
But she's careful, too.
She would have defeated any normal hero by this point.
However, she picked the wrong one this time.
Because now, this hero?
Not the magic sword technique!
Isn't that an upper-tier skill?
It is.
It's called Phoenix Drive.
Oh, yeah.
This hero is unbelievably cautious.
What are you doing?
Don't make me get the hose.
I'm celebrating!
I thought we were done for back there!
Man, oh man.
He smells good enough to eat.
Get off!
Give me a disease!
I am not gonna get you sick!
Come on, just let me have this!
I swear I'm perfectly healthy!
Honestly, though, I'm a little upset with you now.
Why have you been hiding your fake-out skill?
I figured if you had the ability to scan me, then any enemies might be able to do the same.
So I made sure to gain that skill before any others.
So you had it from the start?
I get keeping your true level away from baddies.
But don't you think you could have at least told me?
I mean, I am your partner after all, right?
Even if you kept your big mouth shut, there could be a brain monster.
One peek into your head and we'd be screwed.
Oh no!
A brain monster!
That sounds really scary!
But I know that you would protect me!
You're supposed to be a goddess, aren't you immortal?
You don't need protection.
Not the point!
Cut it out, or I'll cut you.
Go right ahead!
Tear me to pieces!
Hey.
Huh?
Me?
Hey there, Mr. Hero.
We're so glad you saved our town.
I can't believe you beat that beast.
You have our eternal thanks.
He's got the face of a noble man.
Yes, and he's so tall and handsome, too.
Hello, I'm Jamie, and I run the fruit stand.
Please, go and help yourself.
Oh, thank you, Jamie.
Greetings!
I am the mayor of Eduna.
It would be my absolute pleasure to throw a banquet in your honor, so please join me at
my manor.
A welcoming party sure does sound nice.
Want to go?
No, I still have things to take care of, thank you very much.
But then he's heading straight to the next town.
How gallant.
No wonder I'm falling for him.
Uh, hey.
Whatcha doing?
Being safe.
Aren't those the charred remains of the mini bikini demon?
Oh, no.
Casting Hell's Fire!
Not again!
Hell's Fire!
Stand up with the firewrap!
She's a heavenly king.
If a single cell remains, she might regenerate.
I must obliterate her.
Stop it already!
You're scaring everyone off!
Hell's Fire!
Nice.
Time to finish it.
Huh?
Now!
Maximum Inferno!
Inferno!
Hey!
Hell!
See, I love myself.
I love life.
It's a big deal.
By the power of the Goddess Restartate,
may the wounds of this innocent man be healed!
Maximum Inferno!
Hey! How long are you gonna do that?
Please, I humbly beg,
leave our doubted ones!
How did things end up like this?
You were more like a demon lord than a hero!
One kid threw a rock at me,
but I bet you didn't even notice!
We saved them from certain doom,
and yet they treat us so heartlessly.
Lame.
You're one to talk, buddy!
Poor sweet Jamie didn't burn himself, you know!
Not my fault.
Oh, wow, you really are the worst.
Um...
I'm sorry.
We shouldn't have made you leave after you rescued everyone.
Oh, no, there's no need to apologize.
I mean, your town did burn.
Along with a few people, so...
It's not much, but here...
Ooh, money.
You shouldn't be so greedy, Saya!
Try to show some restraint!
What gives?
This isn't very much at all!
If you got any more, then cough it up!
You're no better than a thief!
Here, sir.
It's all I have left.
Hey, mister!
You might be a little weird,
but deep down inside, you're a real good guy!
Oh, Nina.
You're sort of right, and sort of wrong.
He's not a good guy.
Just super weird.
You...
You do realize I'm right here.
You burned down their town and robbed them!
I'm being charitable!
All right!
Let's head off already!
Come on, say goodbye!
Thank you, Miss Nice Lady!
Thank you too, Mr. Weirdo!
Um, sweetie, let's not address people like that.
Listen, don't you think you should start acting a bit more heroic?
Oh.
Look, you still have that pressed flower.
Didn't you say it was a cursed item or something?
Well, that might not be such a bad thing, given our circumstance.
If it attracts enemies, then it might be more convenient for me to hold on to it.
Huh.
What?
Oh, it's nothing.
Yeesh, I really don't get him.
He's so weird.
Okie doke.
Our adventure is just getting started.
Off to the next town!
No, we're going back to the realm.
More training?
Are you kidding me?
When the enemy learns that we beat a heavenly king,
they'll send stronger forces our way.
Okay, but if we don't go to the next town,
then we won't be able to score any good weapons.
Yeah, I would like to buy some new armor, too.
Could you make some for me?
You can make beds and stuff.
I can only create things in the divine realm.
Bringing anything from there is forbidden.
And excessive assistance to human is against divine law.
So you're useless.
Wow!
I healed Jamie's burns in case you forgot!
Medicinal herbs could have done the same.
In other words, your value to society is no greater than that of a leaf.
Are you comparing me to stuff on a tree?
In any case, I'm due for some more training.
Hurry up and open a portal plant, lady.
All right, all right, I hear you.
Wait, why don't you call me?
Good.
Let's go.
We've just taken a few steps forward,
and then a dozen steps back for the second time.
Yeah!
A weirdo hero.
How is this going to work?
Well,OK!
Thank you.
何度目サプライジング
やだねどこ行くの
ここではぐれたらノーマルーン
離さないであなたへお願いは一個だけ
Be perfect please be perfect please
未来はきっと繋いだ糸
遠く細いけど輝いた絆
確かめた追いつけないほらパラサイ
刻んでそっと痛いな一歩
愛想のない沖縄の平
心配
プリズムなの
独り
愛のために
世界の鍵
本当の勇気は
In your hand
抱きしめるよ